Julia.
Julia, where are you?
Can you hear me?
What's going on? Julia!
Please, answer me.
I just need to hear your voice.
Julia, please.
Please, come home.
Please?
Has now been identified
as local woman, Julian Govern.
No comment from the family
who asked for privacy
as the investigation continues.
Come on, I know you're in there.
Wake up.
A moment of your time, sir.
What can I do for you, mister?
You selling something?
I got something I think you
might like.
It's for those times
when Viagra's not working.
I'm not interested. Beat it.
Hey, it's a supplement,
everyone's using it.
Yeah? What is it? What's it
caHed?
It's called "Grow-some-balls."
it might even help you lose some
weight, you fat fuck.
Ah, Frank.
Still flapping your jaws.
Hey, F ran k.
Goddamn, son. You got old.
I'll always be younger
than you, though.
Yeah, well, gravity does suck.
You don't have
to do that any more.
Karen's been gone a long time
now.
Oh, right.
Oh, my, yeah. She would smack me
at the back of the head.
Oh, yes, she would.
Hey, uh, pardon our appearance,
we are in transition.
We had to fire our decorator.
Yeah?
Well, it still looks like a
piece of shit.
Hey.
And you're the same old asshole.
- Yeah.
- 0liver!
Somebody down here wants to see
you.
Whoa!
Fuck me, Roger.
It looks like you had a grown
man that ate your little kid.
It's good to see you, Uncle Frank.
- Wow! Good to see you, buddy.
- Yeah.
Still playing ball, I see?
Yep, what else is there.
Uh. Well, nothing, obviously.
No call from the Bigs yet?
Screw you.
You know what?
I can arrest you.
I could arrest you
for being disrespectful.
No disrespect was intended.
I'm gonna arrest you for
being an ugly son of a bitch.
Yeah, yeah, well, you do that.
In the meantime, tell your kids
to add me on Snapchat.
- It's good to see you!
- You, too.
So let me ask you a question,
Frank.
You here to reminisce,
talk old war stories or what?
No.
I'm here to work.
First one is Linda Gorecki.
She was, uh...
raped, strangled and tortured...
from Skokie about a year ago.
Next is, uh, Eileen Lane.
She was found just outside of
Dallas.
Over the border.
Remember this one?
Yeah, that's Julia Govern.
Found her in that old patch of
woods
over by Highway 77.
And so all these women were
found with this marigold crown,
they were all raped,
tortured and strangled.
All...
blonde, around the same age,
early 30's.
Found in the woods
with a cellphone in the hand.
Final call, to their mothers.
So why here, why now, Frank?
Well, we got a missing person
form a couple towns over, Annabelle Fargo.
She fits the exact description.
And her parents says
she came over here to...
visit a friend, and fell off
the map.
I need more eyes on this, Roger.
All right, buddy.
Anything I could do to help.
I'll put my best guys on it.
Hmm.
You got to be shittin' me.
No judgment.
What you think of me
is none of my damn business.
- Cheers.
- No, that's bad luck.
Hey.
It's all right,
it's all right, it's all right.
It's all right, it's all right.
Calm... calm down. It's okay.
It's okay, look at me.
It's all right,
Do you remember what happened?
- No.
- No, okay.
You're in the ho... It's okay.
It's all right, it's all right,
it's all right. You're safe.
You're safe. You're in the hospital.
You're in Oklahoma City.
But don't worry, It's gonna be okay.
We're gonna take good care of you.
It's okay. Can you calm
down so I can go get a doctor?
Hey, man.
My guys found something
you should see.
- What?
- I'm heading there now.
All right.
All right, text me the address.
I got to get some caffeine in me.
Fuck the caffeine.
Be on your horse, pronto.
Fucking rude awakening.
Any luck?
Well, we have to run some tests.
Could it be retrograde amnesia?
Looks that way.
Anyone come through to claim
him?
No. No missing persons reports.
I did call the station.
Nurse by day.
Sherlock Holmes by night.
Well, I'm a nurse by day
and by night, doctor.
The bandages should be
coming off in a few days.
And we can blast out his photo.
All right, well...
for now, I'll just keep him
talking
- and hopefully...
- Uh, Diana,
your shift ended hours ago.
When was the last time
you had some decent sleep?
Go home, try it.
Doctor's orders.
Doctor Herman, have you
ever had a patient like him before?
Personally, no.
But if it really is retrograde
amnesia,
well, the odds of him recovering
his memories are very slim.
Thanks.
Hi.
- Where'd you learn how to do that?
- I wasn't aware I was doing it.
Here.
It's you rs.
It's quite something.
It's got to be a clue, right?
It's got to mean something?
Nope.
The doctor says you're
gonna make a full recovery.
There's a really good chance.
Well, don't try to remember it
all at once.
Baby steps, John.
That's not my name.
- Sir, do you see the tape?
- FBI. FBI.
- He's all right.
- Oh, sorry.
What do we got?
Well, I'm surprised they let you
in, looking like that.
'Cause I got a bigger badge
than you.
Bigger ego, too. What, you got
no sleep?
Well, thanks to you. What do we
got?
- This better be good.
- What's not good?
We ran the license plate.
The car belongs to the girl.
Annabelle Fargo.
You got to be shittin' me.
Was she driving?
No.
She was in the trunk.
Shit.
We found one guy
that could be a lead.
He was checked in to McNabb
Hospital a few days back.
Nasty car accident.
Goddamn mess.
We should be able to get those
off today.
Now, we got to do this.
I wonder if I was afraid
of needles before,
'cause I sure as shit am now.
- Well, you've been through much worse.
- I told you! He's not ready!
- FBI. I need a word with your patient.
- Uh...
Excuse me!
Julia Govern,
Eileen Lane, Annabelle Fargo,
any of those names ring a bell?
- No, sir.
- No?
Annabelle Fargo was found
stuffed in a trunk...
of her car that you were
driving.
It's got your blood all over it.
- Oh, my god.
- What the fuck is going on?
- Get out of here.
- Move it, move it!
- Get the hell out of here!
- Hold him, Diana!
Can you hear me?
I didn't do nothing.
They're outside...
waiting for you to wake up.
They wanna ask you some
questions.
I don't know how they expect me
to give any answers.
Diana,
can I see you in the hall for a second?
He'll be back with more
questions in the morning.
Dr. Herman.
Thank you for keeping
that dead motherfucker alive.
There's a cop standing guard
tonight.
I need you to go home now.
- But what if something happens? What if...
- This is not up for discussion.
We don't know what he's capable
of.
I want you to get your things
and go home. Now!
Hi, you reached Sheriff Bower.
Please leave your name and number
and the reason you're calling.
- Be a good boy.
- I will.
I'll ge
back to you as soon as I can.
It's me. Frank.
Listen, it's him.
Prints all over the car.
Getthis, the motherfucker
trying to convince folks...
that he's got amnesia.
So there's that.
All right, give me a call back.
You have one new message.
.R' Happy birthday to you I.
Diana! It's your old pal, Tommy.
Hey, do me a favor,
come by and see me soon.
It's been too long.
And happy birthday.
Hope you're having at least a
little fun.
Do something nice for yourself, okay?
How's yo ur sleep?
They're not so good, I remind
you.
Considering what you done.
I didn't do nothing.
"I didn't do nothing."
Yeah, we heard this already.
I don't remember.
So you don't remember?
Yeah, he doesn't remember,
sol guess, that means, free to go.
What's going on?
We're taking you in
to get an X-ray.
To see if your condition
is suitable for...
being taken in to...
So your nurse here is real good
with the play-by-play.
Wow. See that?
Sit down, now.
Good boy.
Come on.
Go on now, come on.
Ready for takeoff?
Papa needs to refuel.
Keep an eye on him.
See you in a second.
You might want
to uncuff him, Officer.
Have you ever put a spoon in a
microwave?
Fuck!
You got a problem?
Steady, keep him steady.
Bank right.
Stop.
Take off your cuffs.
Come on.
Faster!
I need backup.
McNabb County General Hospital.
- You got a car?
- Yeah.
Let's go get your car.
Stay calm,
we're just opening your car.
Okay, get in.
Start the car.
Out of the way!
Damn it!
Oliver!
I'm gonna make some coffee, you
want some?
I'm good, Dad. Thanks.
Sheriff Bower.
You're shittin' me.
All right, no problem.
I'll be there in a minute.
Gotta go, son.
What? Already?
Yeah, you know how it is.
I'll catch you for dinner.
What are you gonna do to me?
Just keep going.
- Stop the car.
- Why?
Now!
Fuck!
You're free to go.
Go wherever you want.
What're you gonna do?
I don't know.
You're definitely not a killer.
You don't need that.
What if you just don't
remember doing those things?
I didn't do it.
'Cause I couldn't do it.
What did you say?
Fuck!
Jesus.
I thought you'd still be
sleeping.
Who are you?
Thomas. Thomas Keller.
No.
Who are you?
0h, uh, I'm Diana's friend.
We went to school together,
so it's been a while.
This is my house.
Where is she?
She'll be back soon.
Hi, guys.
I see you're getting acquainted.
Sure.
Breakfast is served.
Thank you.
Who we are looking for?
White male, about 5'9",
slight build, about 37 years
old.
Any defining features?
He's wearing a long sleeved
white shirt,
blue, uh, pajama pants,
brown suede slippers.
His face is covered in bandages.
He also has very deep, blue
eyes.
It might be your type,
but that's not my type.
All I wanna do is hunt this guy
down.
Appreciate your help.
Are you out of your mind?
They printed your name and
everything.
You're either a kidnap victim
or an accessory to murder.
That's so stupid.
You neverjust show up here,
and with some old friend,
you say, needs time to heal.
I'm sorry.
I'm the only friend you've
ever had and kept, Diana.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I didn't want to get you
involved.
Well... that didn't work!
I'm very much involved!
There's a serial killer
sleeping in my bed!
He didn't do it.
How do you know that?
You know, you look an awful lot
like his other victims.
Yeah, well,
he had the opportunity to kill me.
We were in the woods alone,
and he had a gun, and he didn't do it.
Diana.
Is this about your dad?
Oh, Jesus Christ, don't worry.
Listen, Diana, I know that it
hurts.
You have to forgive yourself.
You have to hand him into the
police.
No. I have to make sure
it doesn't happen again.
Diana.
I love you. I'll do whatever I need
to do to help you get through this.
You can stay here as long as
you need.
Okay? Just...
without him.
He didn't do it.
- How do you know that?
- This is a mistake.
Hey, hey.
Diana.
Di...
Hey, where are you going?
Go back to your friend.
No. I wanna help you.
What do you suggest?
I go to the police,
or they'll help me...
all the way to a lethal
injection?
We need to gather evidence
to prove your own case.
If you're innocent,
you'll be able to prove it.
And what if I'm not?
Hm?
Well, if you're not,
then lethal injection ain't enough.
Right.
Hey, I'm going with you!
So far, you've been a hostage.
You take one more step,
you're an accomplice.
Life without parole.
Well, let's just hope I'm right
about you.
You know how to drive a truck?
It can't be too hard.
I think Diana should drive.
All right.
Thank you...
for this and everything.
Diana.
You always said I should move
on.
Let me.
Hey.
Thank you.
She's too good for this.
I know.
All right, let's go.
So, where to first?
Last crime scene.
If I see it, it might trigger
something.
Where is it?
I don't remember.
Right.
Nice try.
I don't know why I did that.
Whoa. What do you need?
Um, there should be a map in
there.
Map?
Did I wake up in the past?
Well, I'm sure
I can't use my phone.
They're probably tracking it.
All right.
Oh, god.
What?
Oh, my god. There's...
What do we do?
Well, we can't turn back now.
Just stay calm.
I don't think I breathed at all.
Thank god we took the truck.
They must be searching for my
car.
All right.
It should be around here somewhere.
Hey.
Let me go alone.
Just in case.
You promised.
Let's go.
What is it?
I knew her.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Julia Govern lived in McNabb.
So?
So it might be more useful
going there
than just driving up
the next patch of trees.
Right.
I don't want to go in there.
What if her mother recognizes
me?
All right. Well, I'll just go
in.
Some information I can get.
What's going on?
What happened?
I just got a sharp pain in my...
in my stomach.
I just...
I think I need to lie down.
All right. Let's get you to a motel.
Thank you, sir.
We won't be long, buddy.
Oh, it's a nice place.
Not what I expected.
It's right up the alley.
Yeah, maybe she'll, uh,
she'll sell it to you...
to make her bail money.
Pretty bad taste, though, buddy.
I mean, for all we know,
this girl is lying in a field
somewhere, dead.
I don't know. I'm just...
Of course, she's dead, you know.
Well, maybe she's in cahoots
with this guy.
That doesn't sound right.
Wait a minute.
I think we might have something.
Hmm.
Let's get an ID on this guy.
That's right. Might just take
it.
How is this?
You really should get some rest.
Will do.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Right after I check out Julia's.
Are you sure you're gonna be
okay?
Do n't wo rry.
You. I think I know you.
I know you, don't I?
What the fuck?
Who are you?
Get the fuck out of here!
Hey, stop!
Who are you?
Who am I?
Shit!
Fuck!
Jesus. Fuck!
911.
What is your emergency?
Hello?
Is your mother home?
Why?
I was just hoping
I can get a word with her.
You gonna ask about Julia?
Mia!
What have I told you about
opening the door for strangers?
Mia, go to your room.
I'm sorry
to intrude like this. I...
Who are you? What do you want?
I'm a journalist.
I don't talk to journalists
anymore.
Well, it's about
another young woman.
- No.
- She's missing,
and it's just like your
daughter.
Any information you have
could save a life.
I know that this is probably
really hard for you to talk about.
You don't know.
There's just heartbreak, and
hurt, and...
and unanswered questions.
There must be something that...
No.
I'd...
I'd hoped that it would be
solved.
What do you mean "cruel joke"?
Everything you need to know
is in the cemetery.
And all the good ones are there.
If you're good, just stop
looking.
You know, stop digging your own grave
or you'll all end up out there, too.
Criminal clear?
Yes, sir.
What happened here? Are you all
right?
I'm fine.
Can I get a minute alone with
my dad?
What happened?
He was here.
Who was here?
The killer.
What?
Are you sure?
Anything?
No.
I don't know.
She said that I could find
all the answers in the cemetery.
What does that mean?
I wish I could tell you.
She's in distress, Diana.
It's okay.
You're still in recovery.
You should really be in bed.
I already got a nap.
Go ahead.
All right.
Thank you.
Good night, Diana.
Good night, John.
Shot of beer.
What's your name?
Audrey.
I bet you could tell me how to
get to Ridgewood Brook Lane?
Well, maybe.
Just go out to the road.
Take a left, then make a right.
And at the stop sign, you'll
get to Brook.
What time you'd get off?
Two-thirty.
I'll check back around.
Couldn't sleep?
You?
A little.
Look, I'm no nurse,
but I don't think those are good for you.
Just bummed it off
over a friendly drunk girl.
Guess I needed something
to take the edge off.
I really wish we found
something today.
Yeah.
Diana, I want you to do
something for me.
I want you to go home.
To your job, your life.
- I can't.
- Why?
It's got to be better than this
shithole.
When I was 15 years old, we found
out my daddy was having an affair.
We had no idea until his mistress
turned up dead in her apartment.
He was sentenced to life in
prison,
and I swore to god
I'd never talk to him again.
Four years after that,
he hung himself.
Two years later,
new evidence emerged and they
caught the guy who actually did it.
So he died thinking I wanted him
dead, and that's probably why.
What else could you have done?
I could have believed him.
He said the same thing you did.
"I didn't do it 'cause I
couldn't."
That was his only defense.
I won't let that happen to you.
You should go and let him know
we're here.
I'll put this in the garage for
him.
Tom's very particular about his
stuff.
I noticed.
Thomas?
Tom?
I'm sorry, Thomas.
Thomas?
Oh, shit!
Fuck!
What did you do?
Jesus!
Diana, I didn't do this.
You killed Tom?
I couldn't kill Tom!
Don't say that to me.
Diana, listen to me.
You knew what my dad said
and you used it against me.
No.
No, Diana...
Diana!
Who the fuck are you?
Who are you?
Look what I found.
Shit.
So you think that sweet, little
nurse...
killed both her best friend
and our John Doe?
I tell you right now,
that son of a bitch is not our John Doe.
How could you be so sure?
I got a good look at his face.
I know him.
His name is Mark Rosovski.
He was doing time over in
Yankton.
He got parole about a month ago.
What was he in for?
Attempted murder for hire.
Looks to me like we're not the
only ones trying to find this guy.
This whole damn thing, it's starting
to spiral out of control, Frank.
God only knows what we're
gonna end up with this.
Fuckin' mess.
Fuck. Fuck.
Folks, if you see or hear anything
possibly related to this crime,
I want you to contact
local authorities immediately.
- 'Cause I'm still looking for...
- The assailant is supposed
to be armed and dangerous.
Now, I'm asking you to please..
Help us find this killer
before he claims another victim.
We need all
the help we can get, please.
Fulton County Sheriff office.
What's your emergency?
I'd like to speak to Sheriff
Roger Bower.
Uh, one moment, please.
Who is it?
Hello?
I have information on the serial
killer y'all are looking for.
Diana, is this you?
Stay where you are.
I'm coming for you.
Don't you fucking move. Don't...
Hello...
Fuck.
[rips} - Hey!
Oh, don't act like you give a
shit.
Hi.
Is Roger Bower home?
Uh, no. You can find him at the
station.
I was just hoping I could catch him
alone, away from all that.
Well, do you wanna wait for him?
Sure.
I'd love to. Thank you.
I'm Diana.
I'm Oliver. Roger's son.
Thanks.
Oh, I'm sorry about the mess.
We're...
We're redoing a lot.
Oh, it's fine.
Here.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
I hope I'm not intruding.
Nah. It's nice to have
a visitor.
I'm supposed to lay low anyway.
Doctor's orders.
I'd have to agree with him.
But anyway, I'm a nurse.
What happened?
If I may ask.
Home intruder.
If you can believe it.
Same guy who's on the run
for murdering all those women.
Did you hear about it on the
news, or...
Yeah, I did.
I know him, actually.
I actually believed he was
innocent, so...
Can I get you a drink?
My dad makes this lemonade,
it's famous in McNabb.
Sure.
- He can't go that so far, right?
- Frank.
Diana.
It's me.
Well, I'll be damned.
My name is
Detective Michael Winslow.
If you need any more
information,
ask Roger Bower.
You got a location on that call?
He used a burner phone, sir.
Thank you.
That is nice.
Secret family recipe.
I have to say, you look a lot
like my mother.
Really?
Let me show you.
Oh, she is beautiful.
She, uh...
was very beautiful.
When she was alive.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Roger.
Roger!
- Ro... Have you seen Sheriff?
- No, sir.
- Have you seen the sheriff?
- No.
Sheriff Bower here.
Roger.
I just got a really fucked up
phone call.
What is it?
Do you know a guy named Michael
Winslow?
Roger?
Get out of here. Leave me alone!
I'm Michael Winslow, right?
- What do you want from me?
- Right?
Tell me!
Tell me.
I'm trying to remember.
What else do you remember?
The hell you put me and my
father through?
- What did I do?
- You were crazy.
Saying and doing things you
didn't mean.
You were like a brother to me,
and then...
And then what?
You're obsessed with those
girls.
No matter how many times we
told you to.
Oliver.
So now you remember.
Oh, Mikey.
Mikey.
There he is.
Thought you'd never wake up.
What did you do to her?
She just passed out. Don't
worry.
I saved the good stuff for you
to watch.
You really like this one, huh?
Me, too.
I generally prefer blondes,
but...
That's just my type.
Does she look like your mama?
Like all your other victims?
You don't remember
what my mother looks like.
My own best friend.
I was never your friend.
Wow!
And I thought you were lying
about the amnesia.
I guess the upside
to my mother being dead
is that she'll always be young
and beautiful to me.
Why do you feel the need
to kill young women?
I felt awful when I hit
Linda Goreki with my car.
But the funny thing is...
all I could think about was what a
mother would say when she found out.
So I called her,
from Linda's phone.
I was too scared to say
anything, so I...
I just listened.
It was nice to hear
a mother's voice again.
You're sick, Oliver.
You killed five young women.
Right, well...
almost six.
See, I know I'm sick, John.
That's just who I am now.
I can't change it.
I've tried to.
And I can't, so...
Diana.
It's okay.
Shh.
Don't lie to her before she dies.
Dianal
Oliver!
Stay back.
Okay.
- I need you to dial 911.
- All right.
- Dial.
- I got it.
Then leave the house.
Don't come back no matter what
you hear.
Go.
You're a good detective.
Damn good one.
He was sick...
after his mama died.
Five girls, Roger.
Five.
I swear to god, Roger.
I'm gonna find this bastard.
You got to know, it killed me.
When he was doing it.
It tore me up inside.
I vowed that I would protect
that boy no matter what.
I just had no idea how far
I would have to take it.
I knew you were gonna find him.
My son.
The only family I have left
was gonna be taken away from me.
It was either you or him.
Oliver!
Wait!
Damn it.
Roger.
I've located Annabelle Fargo.
In a trunk of a car.
I'm calling you first
'cause you're my friend.
But I've got to call it in.
Look, Mike. No, please.
Not yet.
Look, I just got a call with
Oliver.
He's gonna meet me over
at Lou's Ranch at the warehouse.
I wanna be there when he's
arrested.
Please, we'll take him in together.
I promise, please.
Hero cop...
found the killer.
And I was a good dad.
I tried to take care of it.
Jesus Christ. What have you
done?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Dad, please.
I blacked out.
I couldn't help myself.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
Dad.
And Mike.
Mikey saw me.
He knows!
They're gonna kill me!
They're gonna put me down. I...
I felt like I
didn't have a choice.
It was so damn hard for me,
Michael.
You were like a son to me.
But Oliver...
he was my son.
When you called me,
I sent Rosovski instead.
I told him where you were going.
And hired him to handle the
situation.
The son of a bitch
were sure that you were dead.
He took your badge and ID
like I told him to.
And that was that.
But you must have some kind
of guardian angel
looking out for you, because
well...
here you are.
When I heard that you were stil
out there, still kicking,
[sent him to finish the job.
I knew that if you were alive,
it was just a matter of time
before you caught him again.
Who died in my house?
How'd you fake my death?
I took the body of some sorry
John Doe from the morgue.
And then I planned the gas
explosion.
Then I swapped his fingerprints
for yours.
He became Michael Winslow, and
you...
I thought it was a good thing.
Maybe this whole thing could
finally end for my family.
Making you...
seem like a killer.
And it wasn't a bad idea
somehow.
And now my boy is dead.
Oh, god, help me. I killed my
boy.
And all I can think about...
is that I should've done it a
lot sooner.
You remember...
I taught you how to make this.
Right before you tried to kill
me.
It killed me, too, Mike.
I want you to say my name, RogeL.
The whole thing.
So I can be sure.
Detective Michael Winslow.
You know, they'll be coming
soon.
Yeah.
You go on. You tell them
everything.
Don't worry, I'm not gonna go
anywhere.
I got nowhere left to run to.
Get down
on the ground! Get down!
Down on your knees!
Hold on. Hold up, hold up.
Get him up. Get him up. Get him
up!
I talked to Diana.
Where's the body?
In the basement.
Where's Roger?
Fuck.